-= THE LAST FANTASY =- 荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-= TLF字幕组 =-
翻译｜流星圣殿　　校对｜oksin
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
- 我抓住你了  - 不，不
- I got you.  - No, no, no, no.
我抓住你了，我抓住你了
I got you. I got you.
好了，没事了，别怕
Okay, it's okay. Okay.
上帝啊
Oh, god.
都…都过去了
It's... it's okay.
- 天哪  - 上来
- Oh, god.  - Come on.
噢，天
Oh, god.
披上这个
There you go.
他们都死了
They're all dead.
他把他们都杀死了
He killed them all.
我搞不懂你们这些人
I can't figure you people out.
蜜岛沼泽封了这么多年是有原因的
Honey Island Swamp has been closed for decades and for good reason.
但总有些该死的笨蛋自作聪明
But every now and then, some stupid son-of-a-bitch thinks he knows better.
我懂你的意思
I knew.
我猜，你不相信世上有鬼
Let me guess, you don't believe in ghosts.
你认为维克托・柯劳利只是个传说
You think Victor Crowley is a legend.
我去那儿找我的家人…
I went in there to find my family, my...
我弟弟和我爸爸
My brother and my father.
他把他们全杀了
He killed them all.
他们去那儿干什么？
What the hell were they doing in there?
夜间捕猎
Night fishing.
我爸爸是捕鳄人
My daddy was a gator hunter.
他和我弟弟一旦远离所有人，开始捕猎
He and my brother started pulling in twice their load
就会加倍地超负荷工作
once they start to hunt away from everybody else.
自从我妈妈去世之后，我们需要钱
We needed the money after my momma passed away.
噢，天哪
Oh, god.
现在我孤身一人了
Now I'm all alone.
那你父亲应该更了解这里
Your daddy should have known better.
附近每个猎人都知道，不要走进那片该死的沼泽
Hell, every hunter from around here knows not to go in that damn swamp.
我总是告诫他们“离那鬼地方远点儿！”
I was telling 'em, I say, "Stay the hell out!"
结果他们把我当疯子
Well, they all call me crazy.
以为我脑子有病
They think I'm sick in the head.
来喝几口暖暖身子
Here, you drink this. It's nice and warm.
先做要紧的
First things first.
我们得弄清楚你住哪儿，然后把你送回去
We gotta find out wherever it is you're living and get you there.
再带你看医生
We're gonna get you a doctor.
我觉得我们应该报警
I think I should go to the police.
报警？
The police?
就是填一张失踪报告
What, and fill out one of the missing reports,
像这个地区填的其他几百个人一样？
like the hundreds of others filled out in this area?
你永远都不会从他们那儿听到回信的
You'll never hear back from them.
但我知道他们的尸体在哪儿
But I know where their bodies are.
哼，是啊
Yeah, right.
那些大城市的警察正在往这儿赶呢
Those big city cops are hightailing down here
而且还会在野生动物吃掉尸体之前找到证据
and-and-and they'll find all that evidence before the wildlife eats it.
那我该怎么做？
What am I supposed to do?
再也别回到这儿来
Never come back this way again.
你可真是够幸运的
Hell, you're a lucky girl.
活着从那儿出来了，一个零件也没少！
You got out of there alive and with all your pieces!
小姐，你…你叫什么名字？
Look, miss, what... what's your name?
玛丽贝思
Marybeth.
玛丽贝思・丹斯顿
Marybeth Dunston.
老天啊，你是萨姆森的孩子
Holy Christ, your Samson's kid.
是的
Yes.
出去！
Get out!
- 什么？ - 离开我的房子，快点！
- What?  - Get out of my house right now!
现在就出去！
Get out, now!
你认识我爸爸？
You knew my daddy?
不认识
No.
但是我知道你爸爸都干了什么
But I know what your daddy did
而且我不想和他有半点牵连
and I want nothing to do with it.
我自己好好呆着，鬼魂会离我远远的
I keep myself to myself, and that ghost leaves me be.
但我不能跟你有任何关系
But I can't have nothing to do with you.
出去！
Get out!
可我怎么回家呢？
But how am I supposed to get home?
那扇门外就是洛基路
Out that door is Lodge Road.
你沿着它走半英里
You take it a half a mile down,
到一个加油站，那里你可以搭车
you're gonna find a gas station, you get a ride from there,
但我不能跟你有半点关系，出去！
but I can't have nothing to do with you. Get out!
我…可我不明白这是为什么？
I... but I... I don't understand.
快从我这儿离开，玛丽贝思・丹斯顿
You get out of my house, Marybeth Dunston.
到底是怎么回事？
What's going on?
想知道的话就去找祖比牧师
You want answers, you go see Reverend Zombie.
现在，小姐，请你离开这儿，越远越好
Now, miss, you get far, far away from here
不然我发誓会把你的脑袋打开花
or I swear to God I will shoot you dead.
我没做错什么事
I didn't do nothing wrong.
之前我不知道她是谁
I didn't know who she was.
那不算数
It don't count.
好吧，我们来看看今晚有什么收获
All right, let's take a look at tonight's haul.
都弄到了什么？
What do we got here?
不错嘛
Oh, that's nice.
好
Yeah.
就是它了
That's it.
播放
Play.
我们来看点东西，表演时间到了，对吧？
Let's see something. It's show time, huh?
喔！
Whoo!
- 好了  - 等等，这会上河口海狸吗？
- There you go.  - Wait. Is this gonna be on Bayou Beavers?
没错
Score.
来看看你能干点什么
Let's see what you can do.
很好，因为我想让我爸爸看看
Good, 'cause I want my daddy to see this.
喔！
Whoo!
他妈的，老爸
Fuck you, Dad!
真希望你看到这个
I hope that you're watching this...
哦，好吧
Oh, yeah.
因为你爱丹尼尔多过我
... because you love Danielle more than me
我也希望比尔在办公室…
and I hope that Bill at the office...
转过来，放松点
Roll back, relax a little bit
给我们看看辛迪的另一面…就这样
maybe show us the other side of Cindy... there we go.
哦，你看上去棒极了
Oh, you look fantastic.
真不错，真不错
Really nice. Really nice.
我是不是在哪见过你？
Don't I know you from somewhere?
不，没见过
No, you don't know me.
- 把头发放到…  - 不对！我认识你
- Maybe put your hair up in a...  - No, no! I know you.
你是…你是我五年级的历史老师
You're-you're my History teacher from fifth grade.
- 哦，不是的  - 巴雷特先生
- Oh, no.  - Mr. Barrett.
- 我是夏皮罗  - 是吗…
- I'm Mr. Shapiro.  - Yeah...
嗨，你要去哪儿？
Hey, where are you going?
先生，别跟着我
Mister, leave me alone.
快点，干嘛不把衣服撩起来
Come on. Why don't you to lift up that shirt.
看看衣服下面有什么
Let's see what you got going on under there.
嘿，我才十四岁
Dude, I'm 14.
噢，这可不好
Oh, that ain't right.
好的，好的
Good, good.
我一说开拍，你们就脱下浴巾
Okay, when I say action, you girls drop the towels and, uh,
然后开始互相洗澡
start washing each other.
好的，不
Yeah, no.
好了，姑娘们，脱下浴巾
Okay, girls. Drop the towels.
脱下浴巾
Drop the towels.
让我碰得肝炎的人？
Touch Walking Hepatitis over here?
我不干
I'll pass.
至少我不是个两性人
Well, at least I'm not a hermaphrodite.
两性人，就是今天送你的生僻词
Hermaphrodite, big word of the day for you.
什么是两性人，亲爱的？
What is a hermaphrodite, darling?
我凭什么要说第二遍呢？
Why would I tell you if I just said it?
我当然知道那是什么
Of course, I knew what it is.
- 你大概不知道  - 那你干嘛不继续解释一下？
- You probably don't know what it is.  - Well, why don't you go ahead and explain it?
我为什么要解释？
Why would I need to explain it?
也许你甚至不知道它的意思
You probably don't even know what it is.
那我们就数到“三”一起说？
Why don't we do it on the count of three together?
- 好吧  - 好了吗？
- Fine.  - Okay?
一，二，三
One, two, three.
就是既有阴茎又有子宫的人
Aperson who has a penis and a vagina.
嗯
Ew.
我什么都没做！
I didn't do nothin'!
我甚至都不知道那姑娘是谁！
I didn't even know who that girl was!
短柄斧 II
你想干什么？
What do you want?
嗨
Hi.
嗯，有些事我得跟你谈谈
Um, I need to talk to you about something?
改天再来吧
Come back some other time.
我很忙
I'm busy
什么时候？
When?
下个月
Next month.
不行
No.
我要跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
现在就谈
Now.
好吧，好吧，进来吧，进来吧
All right, all right. Come in. Come in.
最好是重要的事
This better be important.
我是个大忙人
I'm a busy guy.
杰克・克拉克让我来的
Jack Cracker sent me.
什么？
What?
我们吓坏了，太可怕了
(TV) We're so scared, it was terrifying.
我再也不去滑雪了
I'm never going skiing again.
那个疯老头子？
That old whackjob?
那你需要我做什么？
So what do you need from me?
所有人都死了
Everybody's dead.
昨晚在蜜岛沼泽…
Last night in Honey Island Swamp...
蜜岛沼泽
Honey Island Swamp.
你参加了吗？
Were you on that tour?
是的
Yeah.
你怎么知道的？
And how did you know?
发生了什么？
What happened?
那个开船是个蠢货
The boat driver was an idiot.
船抛锚了，柯劳利杀掉了所有的人
He got us stuck, and Crowley massacred everybody.
但我逃走了
But I got away.
肖恩，那个开船的呢，他死了吗？
Shaun, the boat driver, is he dead?
你认识他？
You knew him?
嘘！
Shoo!
是我雇的他
He worked for me.
那是我的船
That was one of my boats.
我不明白
I don't understand.
闭嘴
Shut up.
自从我开店以来这么多年
No one's been able to run tours out of this swamp for years,
没有人能跑下来这个沼泽的旅游业务
not since I've had this shop.
从来没有
Ever.
我不能，谁都不能
Not me, not anybody.
所以我被迫在我另一个店的后门搞旅游
So I was forced to run tours at the back door of one of my other shops.
世道艰难，挣一点是一点
Times are tough and money is money.
你跟我爸爸做的差不多
You sound just like my daddy.
你爸爸是谁？
Who's yourfather?
萨姆森・丹斯顿
Samson Dunston.
你是萨姆森・丹斯顿的孩子？
Samson Dunston's kid?
是的
Yes.
你爸爸还好吗？
Well, how is old Samson doing?
他死了
He's dead.
主啊
Grace.
柯劳利杀了他
Crowley got him
还有我哥哥
and my brothertoo,
后来杰克・克拉克被我吓着了
and then Jack Cracker freaked out on me.
知道我是谁之后差点冲我开枪
Practically shot me when he found out who I was.
他说你会告诉我我爸爸做的事
He said that you would be able to tell me what my daddy did.
萨姆森・丹斯顿
Samson Dunston.
- 萨姆森・丹斯顿已经不在了  - 求你了
- Samson Dunston's gone.  - Please.
你都知道些什么？
What do you know?
一些小道消息
Same thing that everybody else whispers
我猜是关于林区的
about these backwoods, I suppose.
那事发生的时候我只是在附近
Only I was around when it actually happened.
什么事发生的时候？
When what happened?
很久以前
A long time ago
在你出生之前，那时候我还是个小男孩
before you were born when I wasjust a boy.
有一个叫做托马斯・柯劳利的人
There was a man named Thomas Crowley.
他就住在蜜岛沼泽
He lived out there in Honey Island Swamp
还有他的妻子夏恩
with his wife Shyann.
他们与世隔绝
They lived alone.
没有孩子，就他们两个人
No kids, just the two of them.
夏恩病了，大概是胃癌之类的
Shyann was sick,
病魔让她日益消瘦
some sort of stomach cancer eating her up slowly
慢慢夺走了她的生命
and gradually taking its time.
我听到的是
Now the way I always heard it
夏恩有个护士叫丽娜
Shyann had a nurse named Lena
是个漂亮的法裔女人，会过来照顾她
a beautiful Cajun woman who would come by to tend to her.
在夏恩病逝前的那段时间里
And over the long months of Shyann's passing,
托马斯和丽娜越来越亲近
Thomas and Lena got closer.
过分亲近了
Too close.
你可以说托马斯是个骗子或异教徒
Call Thomas Crowley a cheat, call him an infidel,
但在那种情况下
but given the circumstances,
生活里只有悲伤和不幸
the entire situation was nothing but sad and tragic.
妻子如死人般过了那么多年
With his wife as good as dead for so many years,
痛苦的情感需要释放
it was only a matter of time until the pain and suffering of his own emotions
这是迟早的事
needed to be addressed.
起初的一年托马斯和丽娜一直偷偷摸摸的
It took almost a year of Thomas and Lena carrying on in secret
他们希望夏恩平静的死去
before the day came when Shyann finally found peace from her suffering.
而她得死并不安详
But the moment was not so much a release
简直就是噩梦
as it was a nightmare.
不
No!
她对托马斯・柯劳利和她的情妇丽娜下了诅咒
She put a curse on Thomas Crowley and his mistress, Lena,
诅咒他们
a curse that would not only damn them
甚至诅咒丽娜肚子里的私生子
but the bastard child that was already growing in Lena's belly.
不
No.
据说维克托・柯劳利出生的那一天
They say that on the day Victor Crowley was born,
沼泽里将悲鸣不断
the swamp mourned.
树木哭泣
The trees wept.
生命染病而死
The wildlife became sickly and died.
他的降生好像瘟疫的到来
His presence was like a pestilence
周围到处是死亡
that turned the area into death.
用力，就出来了
Come on. There it is.
用力，用力
Push, push.
快了
Push. There it is. Come on.
用力点，再用力点
Come on. One more.
就好了
Here it comes.
加油，加油
One more, one more.
维克多・柯劳利带着可笑的肿瘤和疾病出生
Victor Crowley was born ridden with grotesque tumors, disease
还有痛苦
and pain.
让我看看，让我看看他！
Let me see. Let me see it!
一个活生生的怪物
A living monster.
而丽娜…
And Lena...
有人说她看到孩子的第一眼就死了
Some say she died the moment she laid eyes on her child.
传说会让你相信
Now the legend would have you believe that Mr. Crowley
克劳利先生是为了保护孩子才把他藏起来的
kept his son hidden away to protect him,
事实上他是为了掩盖他的错误
but what he was really hiding
他的背叛
was his mistake, his infidelity
和他受到的诅咒
and his curse.
很多年来托马斯一直尝试去爱他的怪物儿子
Over the years, Thomas Crowley learned to love his monster of a son.
两个人与世隔绝
With just the two of them being hidden away,
上帝给了他们片刻宁静
he made his peace with God.
在万圣节的那天晚上…
And on that fateful Halloween night...
托马斯为了救出自己的儿子
Thomas tried to save his son
他用短斧想要劈开门
by chopping through the door with a hatchet
而意外发生了
And by accident,
他不小心砍死了自己的孩子
killed his only son.
滚出来！
Get out here!
滚出来接受惩罚！
Get out here and get what's coming to you!
你们躲不了一辈子！
You can't hide forever!
你们杀了我的儿子
You killed my son.
犯了错的孩子一直躲在父母的身后
The children responsible hid behind their parents,
什么也不承认
denied everything
托马斯・克劳利在痛苦中度过了余生
and left Thomas Crowley to live out the rest of his days in anguish.
你们杀死了我的儿子
You killed my son.
一些年后，他也死了
Years later, he finally passed
备受折磨的一生终于结束
and the torture of this life was over.
而维克多・柯劳利却成了悲剧人物
But Victor Crowley would become one of the most tragic
以及路易斯安那州的一个令人心碎的传说
and heartbreaking tales of Louisiana.
一个困在沼泽里的被杀死了的人
A man trapped in the night he was killed,
却还每晚出来游荡
still out there, wandering the swamp
找他的爸爸
each night trying to find his daddy.
没人知道死了多少人
No one knows the body count,
但自从维克多死后
but for years after he died, fishermen,
渔民，捕鳄人
Gator hunters,
还有那些来打探传说的人
And those who were just too foolish to heed the tales,
都在沼泽里消失了
all disappeared in that swamp
被肢解，谋杀，屠戮
mutilated, murdered, massacred
被这个鬼魂魄撕成碎片
and torn to pieces by the ghost
成为维克多的刀下魂
of Victor Crowley.
这和我有什么关系？
What does that have to do with me?
你的父亲萨姆森
Your father, Samson,
是那三个谋杀了维克多的孩子中的一个
was one of the three kids who murdered Victor Crowley.
尽管是意外
An accident, yes,
但这个悲剧使得蜜岛沼泽
but a tragedy that has left Honey Island Swamp
永远的被维克多的鬼魂缠绕
cursed with the ghost of Victor Crowley forever.
啊
Uh.
我从没有…
I... I never...
当然了
Of course.
你怎么可能知道？
How could you know?
你怎么知道我父亲参与其中的？
How do you know that my dad was involved?
因为如果当时我胆子够大，就和他们一起去了
Because if I had been brave enough, I would have been out there too.
我是你父亲的老熟人
I'm an old acquaintance of Samson.
- 柯劳利跟着我们的那天晚上…  - 你看见他了？
- When Crowley came after us last night...  - You saw him?
是的
Yes.
他看着我
He looked at me
就好像认识我一样
like he knew me.
或许他能感觉出你是谁
Perhaps he could sense who you really were.
或许那只是我的感觉罢了
Perhaps it was all on your mind.
维克多的复活只能用超自然来解释
Victor Crowley is what's known in the paranormal world as a repeater.
他的悲剧和过早死亡，逼迫他重新体验那个时刻
His tragic and untimely death has left him forced to relive
一晚又一晚，一次又一次
that moment night after night, over and over.
他所知道的只有恐惧，和向踏进沼泽的人复仇
All he knows is the fear and revenge towards anybody who steps foot in that swamp.
你知道这一切都是真的
You knew all this was real
却仍然送无辜的人去那里旅游？
yet you still sent a tour boat full of innocent people in there?
为了什么？
For what?
为了什么？为了钱吗？
For what? For money?
肖恩
Shaun.
他不该那么靠近的
He wasn't supposed to get that close.
他不该无缘无故停在那里
He wasn't supposed to stop for nothing.
现在我的船走进沼泽几个月了
Now I've had boats go into that swamp for months now,
两个月了，没令人担心过
two months now, with no worries.
你去那儿，除了知道这个传说之外
Besides you knew the legend.
也知道你父亲做的事
You went in there knowing the story as did your father,
我去是为了…
I went in...
任何人都没你们清楚
who more than anybody should have known better.
我是去找他们
I went in there to find them
而且我找到了
and I did!
没几个人见过维克多的真面目
Not many people have seen the face of Victor Crowley
还能活着回来说
and lived to tell about it.
你可真够幸运的
Consider yourself lucky.
幸运？
Lucky?
我的家人都死光了！
My family is gone!
对你的不幸我感到遗憾
I'm sorry for your loss.
- 带我回去  - 什么？
- Take me back there.  - What?
我不能把他们留在那儿
I can't leave them there. Please.
求你了，我就是想把他们带回来
Please. I just wanna take them home.
你想要的是复仇才对
What you want is revenge.
这可不是个好主意，玛丽贝思・丹斯顿
It's a bad idea, Marybeth Dunston.
不是个好主意
Bad idea.
求你了
Please.
求你，我只是想埋葬家人
Please. I just wanna bury my family.
如果能顺便解决了那个怪物
And if I can take that monster out with me,
那就更好不过了
then all the better.
你杀不了他的
You can't kill him.
他会一次次复活
He'll just be reborn.
他会恢复到死前的状态
He's supposed to return to the state he was when he was killed.
鬼魂是无法被杀死的
You can't kill a ghost.
或许我杀不了他
Or maybe I can't.
或许我可以
Or maybe I can.
我可以用斧子劈烂他的脸！
But I am gonna bury that hatchet deep into his fucking face!
你还是要我到警察局告发你？
Or would you rather I go to the police and tell them about your swamp tour business?
告诉警察他们可以在哪里找到游客的尸首
Maybe tell them where to find the bodies of a boat full of tourists
那些非法运送的游客？
that you sent in there illegally, huh?
行，行，行
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
好吧
All right.
什么？
Yes?
你想要复仇？
You want revenge on Victor Crowley?
我会帮你找到它
I want you to find it.
你会带我回去？
So you'll take me back in there?
但是我有条件
But I have some conditions.
我们不能独自去那里，我们需要帮助
We're not going in there alone. We need help.
我们需要枪
We need guns.
有几个人跟着去会更安全
And there's a few specific people that I feel safer having along.
你要你今晚带我去就行
Fine, if you take me back in there tonight.
今晚两点我们在这会面
Now, you meet me here at 2 o'clock.
我要打几个电话
I have some phone calls to make.
我得组织个狩猎队之类的
I'm gonna gathertogether a little hunting expedition of sorts.
那个怪物一挂，我就能安心做生意了
With that ghost gone, I can clear that swamp.
你知道我不关心你的沼泽旅游生意
You know, I don't care about your swamp tour business.
我不关心你的钱
I don't care about your money.
我只想带家人回家
I just want to bring my family home.
- 你要带回我的家人…  - 我说过了…可以
- If you think that bring...  - I said... yes.
但是我建议你不要单独跟我去
But you know, I think it would be better if you didn't go in there alone.
有没有人可以跟你一同去
Do you have somebody you can bring,
男朋友或者叔叔之类的？
boyfriend or an uncle perhaps?
我不想把任何我认识的人牵扯进来
I'm not bringing anybody else I know into this.
嗯哼
Uh-uh.
你能带个人来的话我会更放心
I'd feel better if you brought somebody,
带个亲人过来
if you brought another family member with you.
不
No.
那没的谈了
Then no deal.
如果我带叔叔过来你就让我们去是吗？
So if I bring my uncle back, then you will take us?
我就是这个意思
That's what I said.
我两点回来
I'll be back at 2:00.
我等你
I'll be here.
贾斯丁！
Justin!
滚过来！
Get your butt down here!
老板？
Yeah, boss?
你打算什么时候告诉我
When were you gonna tell me
你哥哥没开船回来？
that your brother didn't bring the boat back?
他还没回来？
Oh, he didn't?
肖恩昨晚没开船回来？
So Shaun didn't bring the boat back last night?
嗯哼
Uh-uh.
他是个新手
Look, he'sjust new at this.
我保证没问题的，或许他现在已经开回来了
I'm sure things are fine... he's probably got the boat back by now.
那本该是你的活，他替你的班儿了
That was your shift. He was covering for you, okay?
他没回来，所有事都不对
He didn't bring the boat back and everything's not all right.
为什么？发生什么事了？
Why? What... what's wrong?
我们得去一趟，把船弄回来
We gotta go out there and recover my boat.
肖恩还在沼泽里？
Shaun's still in the swamp?
显然是
Apparently.
他还好吗？
Is he all right?
我保证他会没事的
I'm sure he will be all right.
我要你出去召集一批猎手和渔民
I need you to go out and organize a group of hunters and fishermen,
熟悉沼泽环境的人
people that know the way around the swamp.
我有一个计划
I got a proposition to make them
而且你要确保这个人一定要来
and you make sure that this name is on the list.
我们要进行小探险了
We're going on a little expedition.
这算一种商业宣传吗？
Is this like a publicitything forthe shop?
差不多吧
Something like that.
你好？
Hello?
谁在哪？
Who's there?
你好？
Hello?
玛丽贝斯？萨姆森？
Marybeth? Samson?
鲍勃叔叔？
Uncle Bob?
我就过去
I'll be right down.
你父亲是个好人，你知道的
Your father was a good man, you know that.
他一直是我最好的朋友
He's always been my best friend.
尽管这些年我住在北边，但我们一直保持联络
Even all those years I lived up north, we'd talk all the time.
祖比牧师说
Reverend Zombie said dad was
爸爸对维克多・柯劳利的死负有责任
one of the people responsible for Victor Crowley's death.
真的吗？
Is that true?
祖比牧师？
Reverend Zombie?
你怎么会跟那个恶棍有接触？
Why are you talking to that low-life?
他是个小偷和骗子
He's a thief and crook
开假的巫毒商店，卖假纪念品
with his bogus voodoo shops and his fake souvenirs.
他说他认识与此事有关的人
Well, he said that he knew the people that were involved.
纯属胡说八道
He's full of horse-shit.
- 祖比牧师说…  - 祖比牧师说！
- Reverend Zombie said...  - Reverend Zombie said!
你居然这么称呼他？
Why do you call him that?
看在上帝的份上，他的真名是克利夫・华盛顿
His name is Clive Washington for Christ's sake.
他唯一擅长的就是当一个混蛋
The only thing he's reverend of is being an asshole.
你以前知道克劳利真的存在吗？
Did you know that Victor Crowley was real?
- 他不存在  - 我看见他了
- He's not real.  - I saw him.
他在我面前杀了所有的人
He murdered everyone in front of me.
让警察处理这件事
Let the police handle this.
- 首先…  - 不！
- First things...  - No!
你以为我在说谎？
So you think that I'm lying?
让我们出去透透气
Let's take a ride.
我们去趟医院，顺便告诉警察你经历的事情
We can go to the hospital and you can tell the cops all about it.
我要和祖比牧师回沼泽
I'm going back to the swamp with Reverend Zombie.
我死也不会同意的
Over my dead body are you going to that god damn swamp.
听我说，小姑娘
Now you listen to me, young lady.
你父亲死了之后
With yourfather gone,
现在我要对你负责，绝对禁止你做危险的事情
I'm responsible for you now and I absolutely forbid you
要让你远离他或者这片沼泽
to have anything to do with him or that swamp!
他建议你跟我一块去
He suggested that I bring you along.
- 他真这么说了？ - 嗯
- He did, didn't he?  - Mm-hmm.
跟我来吧，你会看到这一切都是真的
Come with me. You'll see Victor Crowley is real.
我们出去走走
Let's take a ride.
我们可不可以先等等？
Can we wait?
求你了，我会去报警的
Please. I will go to the police.
我什么都听你的
I will do whatever it is that you think that we need to do.
我只是想单独呆一会
I just... I just really need to be alone for a bit.
快点儿
Come on.
求你了
Please.
求你了，鲍勃叔叔，我就待一会儿
Please, Uncle Bob, just a few hours.
好吧，我一小时后回来
All right, I'll be back in an hour.
我自己会报警的
I'll call the police myself.
- 统统告诉警察  - 好的
- Get to the bottom of this.  - Okay.
玛丽贝斯
Marybeth,
向我保证你会远离那个骗子牧师
please promise me you'll stay away from Reverend Zombie.
我保证
I promise.
进来吧，我看见你了
Ah-ha, come on in. I see you!
欢迎来到祖比牧师的巫毒之屋
Welcome to Reverend Zombie's House of Voodoo.
拿一块免费的土豆片，然后找个座位坐下
Grab a complimentary Chips Ahoy and take a seat.
快点儿，请坐
Hurry. S'il vous plait.
会议马上就开始了
The meeting is about to start.
是的，哈哈
Yes. Ha-ha.
早上好，先生们，欢迎来巫毒之屋
Bonjour, monsieur. Welcome to the House of Voodoo.
请坐，别忘了我们今天护身符和药水特价
Take a seat and don't forget we have a sale on charms and potions today only.
别装腔作势了，混蛋
Drop the phony accent, asshole.
我不是为了该死的观光来的
I ain't no god damn tourist.
来点土豆片？
Chips Ahoy?
滚蛋
Fuck off.
嘿
Hey.
嘿，你想不想得到邮寄目录？
Ah, he-hey, uh, did you wanna get on the mailing list?
我的意思是，你可以只给我你的电话
Um, you can just gimme your number, I mean.
我是说，你不用给我，但是…
I mean you don't have to gimme but you...
婊子
Slut.
雷登？
Layton?
天啊，没想到在这儿见到你
Oh, my god, I didn't expect to see you here.
别这样，艾弗里
Come on, Avery.
什么？
What?
你这来干什么？
What are you doing here?
给五百块呢，为什么不来？
They said 500 bucks. Why not?
我们就这么打招呼？
Okay, so this is how we say hello now?
别这样
Please.
你电话收不到信息了？
Your phone don't get messages anymore either?
你知道我为什么来这儿？
You know why I'm here?
我需要者五百块来准备婚礼
I need the $500 to help pay for my wedding.
我的婚礼，艾弗里
My wedding, Avery.
我没法跟你在一起了
I am not getting into this with you.
我还单身哦
I'm single.
很好，很好
Ho, ho, ho. Tres bein, tres bein!
欢迎各位的到来
Welcome. All right, everyone.
十分感谢，或者就像法国人说的
Thanks or as the French say,
感谢大家能在这么短时间内过来
merci for coming down here on such short notice.
我知道你们都很忙
I know you are all busy people.
什么事？
Yes?
这些饼干是这么回事？
Hey, man, what's the deal with cookies?
每人一块还是可以多拿点？
Is it just like one each or could we get some more or what's up?
我们会提供更多饼干，但首先我们能否…
I have more cookies but first, can we, uh...
那我们现在可以要吗，还是会后？
Okay, so do we get them now or like after the meeting?
什么时间可以吃？
Or... what's the time stamp on them cookies there?
算了
Fine.
给你
There it is.
祝你好胃口
Bon appétit.
下午好各位
Good afternoon, everybody.
很高兴能看到很多熟悉的面孔
Good to see so many friends with familiar faces here today.
约翰
John.
克里特斯
Cleatus.
特伦特
Trent.
叫大家来是给大家找了个活儿
I brought y'all here today to make you an offer, to offer you ajob.
有一笔快钱，就在今晚
It's a quick gig. We do it tonight.
只要入伙，就有五百块
And for those of you thatjoin me, there's $500 in it for you.
是现金支付对吧？
And I assume the money will be in cash?
我们这儿可没人信得过你的支票
Not that any of us here don't trust a check from you,
我们要钱，不要白条
it's that we really want to get the money.
现金支付，工作完成之后
In cash, when thejob is done.
昨晚我有一艘船在沼泽失踪了
Last night, I lost one of my tour boats out there in that swamp,
所以我准备带一队人帮我找回来
so I'm putting together a group of sorts to go in there,
当然也打点儿猎
retrieve my boat, and in addition, go on a little night hunt.
找船要用这么多人？
Why do you need this many people to find a boat?
如果你不再打断我，我会告诉你的
If you stop interrupting me, I'll tell you.
五百块当然不会是仅仅找船那么简单
Now, of course, I'm not offering you y'all $500 just to retrieve a boat.
跟你们说实话吧
I'm gonna be honest with you.
还有更危险的事情要你们做
There's more to it and it could be dangerous.
伙计，有牛奶吗？
Hey man, do y'all got any milk?
- 什么？ - 牛奶啊
- What?  - Milk, man.
配饼干的牛奶
Milk forthe cookies, man.
牛奶，牛奶？
Milk. Milk?
没牛奶
No milk.
我们要去蜜岛沼泽
We're going to Honey Island swamp.
蜜岛沼泽关闭了，我们去不了
Honey Island's closed. We can't even go in there.
我知道，所以才给你们开价这么高
I know that. That's why I'm offering y'all $500,
除此之外，我愿意负所有的法律责任
and in addition, I'm willing to take on full legal responsibility
以防你们担心惹上政府的麻烦
in case there'll be any trouble with the authorities.
因此你们没有任何麻烦
So it won't be any risk to any of y'all.
我们到底在哪里打猎？
What exactly are we gonna be hunting?
就要提到地点了
I'm getting to that.
你们也知道，那里已经被关闭了很多年
As you know that swamp has been closed and condemned for too many years,
严重损害了我的旅游生意
and it's been crippling my tourism business
你们的打猎也大受影响
and it's been stopping those of you who make your living hunting
那里野生动物很多
an entire area rich with wildlife.
因此我建议我们一起打猎
So I'm proposing we put a little hunt,
证明给别人那里是安全的，没什么可怕的
go in there and prove once and for all that there's nothing to fear.
我们到底去猎什么？
What are we hunting?
维克多・克劳利
Victor Crowley.
等等，等等，等等，等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute.
等一下
Now hold on, now.
请等一下！
Hold on!
听我说，听我说
Now, listen to me. Listen to me.
如果那里真的有疯子
Now if there really is some maniac living up there,
我们把他们灭了，让这个地区再次安全起来
we just go in there, take them down and make the area safe again.
你们知道那只是个传说
All right, now, y'all know that's just a story
我们只需要去把这个骗人的传说揭穿罢了
so we go in there and put an end to all this swamp water stupidity.
我不去
Not I.
回来，回来，大家别走…
Now, now, now, now. Come on. Come on, everyone...
嘿，回来，大个子
Hey, come on now, big guy.
特伦特，你去哪儿？
Trent, where you going?
你怕什么？
You scared of something?
你知道我什么都不怕的
You know I ain't scared of nothing,
但是我不想和一群上蹿下跳叽叽喳喳的家伙
but I ain't about to go messing around in that swamp
一起为了五百块在沼泽里浪费时间
with a crew of stomp-jumping pecker woods for no 500 bucks.
嘿，我需要你，好吗？
Hey, I need you, all right?
你是这里枪法最准的
Now you're the best shot around here.
所以我才叫你
You know that. That's why I called for you.
我不想为了五百臭钱去冒险
I ain't riskin' my hide for 500 stinking dollars.
预付五百
Five hundred dollars up front just for you.
你知道我的经历
Clive, you know my history.
我不想有麻烦
I don't want no more trouble.
我知道上次你醉酒驾车之后琼就离开了你
I also know that after your last DUI, Joan left you, took the house,
拿走了你一半的财产，还搭上了别人
half of everything you have, hanging on a hook.
我说的不是这个经历
That ain't the history I'm talking about.
一千块现金，预付五百
One thousand dollars cash, $500 right now up front,
另五百早上给你
$500 in the morning.
就一晚上，我们都去，怎么样？
One night and we'll all be together, huh?
解决一切问题，我们…
Anything bad goes down, we...
就离开
leave.
嗯？
Hmm?
好吧
Yeah.
有什么事？
May I help you?
你一定是玛丽贝斯的叔叔吧
Oh, you must be Marybeth's uncle.
我是祖比牧师
I'm Reverend Zombie.
我是萨姆森的朋友，只是咱们没正式见过面
I was a friend of Samson, but you and I never officially met.
我对你不感兴趣
I don't care to know you.
我是来照顾她的
I'm here to look after the young lady.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是想…
I... I just need...
如果你非要去，我就和你一起
I'll do this with you if... if it's what you need to do right now,
我会在你身边
I'll do it with you.
但是必须要收集了你家人的遗骸就走
But then we gather up your father and your brother and we come back here.
别去管那个维克多・克劳利
No more of this Victor Crowley shit.
你要听我的话
You gotta listen to me.
一直在我身边，不能离开我的视线
You can't leave my side, you can't leave my sight,
我说离开就得离开
and when I say it's time to go, we leave.
谢谢你
Thank you.
老兄，谁是维克多・克劳利？
Hey, man. Who's Victor Crowley?
他什么都不是
Well, he's nothing,
本地的恶魔故事，说一个疯子在蜜岛沼泽出没
a local boogeyman story about a retarded maniac who haunts Honey Island.
为了吓唬小孩子别去沼泽
Peoplejust use it to keep kids away from the swamp.
类似于杰森・福尔西斯？
You mean like a Jason Voorhees or something?
就那意思
Something like that.
我八岁的时候住在回声幽谷
When I was eight, I lived in this town called Glen Echo.
- 我们的鬼故事是关于一个叫莱斯利・弗农的…  - 嘘
- Our ghost story is about this man named Leslie Vernon...  - Shh.
既然胆小鬼都走了
Now that we've weeded out the gullible, the cowards,
现在该谈谈生意了
I could finish my offer.
五百美元
Five hundred dollars
只要今晚跟我把船带回来就可以拿到
just forjoining me forthe night, bringing back my boat.
还有五千美元，给取了维克多人头的人
Five thousand dollars for the head of Victor Crowley.
我们连他存不存在都不知道，怎么找到他？
Yeah, but how are we suppose to know if we found him if he's not a real dude?
如果你找到了他
If you find him,
你就会知道了
then you'll know.
妈的，你看看这些鳄鱼？
God damn, would you look at all the gators around here?
简直就像个该死的农场
It's like a fucking farm.
我猜牧师说的就是这个
I guess that's what Reverend Zombie's talking about.
这么多鳄鱼
Look at all these.
没人来抓它们
Nobody here to take 'em.
我不会空手而归的
Hell, I ain't leaving here empty handed, that's for sure.
你叫什么？
What's your name?
查德
Chad.
克里特斯
Cleatus.
真的？
Really?
是啊，我知道
Yeah, I know.
我父母是乡下人
My parents were true rednecks.
我还有个弟弟叫“现金”[Cash]呢
I got a brother named Cash.
比克里特斯酷多了
It's cooler than Cleatus.
没有冒犯的意思
No offense.
没事
None taken.
但是，查德，你的名字也够烂的啊
But Chad, that's, uh, that's a real douche bag name.
你说是吗？
You know that, right?
比“偷溜”[Skip]强多了
It's betterthan Skip.
我弟弟就那名字
That's my little brother.
乍得和偷溜？
Chad and Skip?
你俩是不是学校光受气了
God damn, you two must have had your asses handed to you in school.
的确如此
Yeah, we did.
我们不跟他们一起坐船怎么样？
So how come we don't get ride in the boat with them boys up there?
去论去哪儿我都开自己的船
I take my own boat wherever I go.
这是为什么？
What the hell for?
万一我泡上妞呢
In case I hook up.
荒郊野外的你泡谁啊？
Who are you gonna hook up with out here?
她
Her.
噢，上了她
Aw, fuck her.
饼干、鸡肉和肉汁
Biscuits and chicken and gravy,
and biscuits and chicken and gravy,
鸡肉和饼干
and chickens with the biscuits
饼干、鸡肉和肉汁
on the gravy with the biscuits and the chicken.
我要点饼干，因为饼干就是我
Want some biscuit for the biscuit is me.
带这么一帮暴徒干什么？
So what's with a whole lynch mob?
人多安全
Safety in numbers.
我知道他们大多数人觉得那个故事只是个玩笑
I know most of these folks think this whole story is ajoke,
但如果真有状况
but if something bad goes down,
周围有一帮枪手也不错
I'd rather be surrounded by the big guns.
不是吗？
Wouldn't you?
你不是说杀不了他吗？
I thought you said you couldn't kill him?
但如果传说是真的
Ah, but if the legend is true,
万一真的有鬼魂
then there really is a ghost or maybe not.
昨晚我打伤了他
I hurt him last night.
我开枪打他，捅他烧他
I shot him, I stabbed him, I burned him.
他一个劲向前
He kept coming.
但是你还是伤了他
But you hurt him.
他每次都被击退
He went down every time.
都会感到疼痛
He felt pain.
所以或许关键就在于对要打得狠一些
Then maybe the thing is to hit him even worse.
狠狠地打，把他脑袋拧，他就活不了了
Hit him so hard, take his head off, so he can't come back.
你叫他什么来着？复活者？
What did you call him, a repeater?
那不就意味着他第二天晚上又会回来？
But doesn't that mean that he will just come back again the next night?
我没有答案，只有推断
I don't have answers, only theories.
但是我只能这么假设
But I have to assume that, uh, if we take off his head,
砍掉脑袋，他就会挂掉
then he can't come back at all.
大家处于危险却全然不知
All these people are in danger and they don't even realize it.
老大
Boss.
他，他…嘿，老大！
He-he... hey, boss!
肖恩下船了吗？
Did Shaun get off the boat?
我肯定他们没事
I'm sure they're okay.
所以我们才过来
That's why we're here.
嗨？
Sup?
嗨
Hi.
我是弗农
I'm Vernon.
玛丽贝斯
Marybeth.
你到这个鬼地方来干什么？
What you doing out here in this bullshit?
总之不是来约会的，我只能说这么多
I'm not looking for a date, I can tell you that much.
哦，无意冒犯，我只是想表示一下友好罢了
Ooh, no disrespect, I'm just trying to be friendly.
抱歉
Sorry.
我刚刚过了很糟糕的一天
I'm just having a really bad day.
你要做的是别这么紧皱着眉头
Well, what you need to do is turn that frown upside down.
谢谢，弗森
Oh, thanks, Vernon.
跟我亲热吧
Make out with me.
什么？
What?
在船上当着这么多人？
On this boat, in front of all these people?
是的
Yeah.
不要
Don't.
好吧，好吧
Okay, man, okay.
船上有怪物，伙计
There're some freaks on this boat, man.
那个小巫婆怎么回事？
What's up with that Blair witch, man?
她的嘴是不是被蜘蛛网封住了
I'd tap that but she probably got cobwebs sealing it up.
如果我能让她开口说话的话
Even if I did hit that,
是不是就会有一群蝙蝠从她嘴里飞出来
a bunch of bats probably come flying out of it.
巫毒
Voodoo.
魔法
Magic.
睁大你们的眼睛
Just keep your eyes open.
睁大
Open.
今晚会很漫长
This will be a long night.
真是一片死寂
Man, it is dead in here.
我们要去的地方比这里茂密的多
Where we're going, it gets much thicker.
快到傍晚了
It's almost nightfall.
前进
Let's move!
- 还要多远到房子？ - 什么房子？
- Hey, how much farther to the house?  - What house?
我不确定，眼前的景象对我来说都差不多
I'm not exactly sure. This all looks the same to me.
我们没走太远
We didn't walk far.
只是不确定在哪儿下船
I'm just not exactly sure where we got off.
你们下船干什么？
Why'd you guys get off the boat?
我不想逗留
Well, I don't wanna linger.
- 咱们去房子里吧  - 什么房子？
- Let's get to the house.  - What house?
我父亲和哥哥在棚子里
My daddy and my brother are in the shed.
去棚子里干什么？
Why were they in the shed?
什么房子？
What house?
这儿真吓人
It's scary out here.
那是因为别人想要你这么觉得
Oh, that'sjust 'cause people want you to think it's scary.
这和其他沼泽没什么分别
It's no different than any other swamp.
你有没有注意到这里几乎没有鸟儿？
Have you noticed that there's hardly even any birds?
无所谓
Doesn't matter.
别让那个小丑把你唬了
But don't let that clown spook you.
你要做的就是在这儿转一晚上
All you gotta do, hang out here for a few hours,
然后拿钱回家
collect our money, and go home.
见他的鬼
Screw that.
我要灭了克劳利那怪物
I'm taking out that Crowley monster guy.
五千块够我还债了
5000 bucks, I could be out of debt.
这儿高手这么多，你想夺魁？
Ha! Out of all these guys, you'll get him?
我比你枪法好
I'm a better shot than you.
才不是呢
That's not true.
两年前花园区的那场比赛
Okay, Garden District Fair, two years ago.
我当时喝多了你才赢的
I was drunk and I let you win.
就像冰球和游泳比赛那两次一样？
Right, kinda like how you let me win at air hockey and at pool?
我当时病了
I was sick.
你真可爱
You're adorable.
该死的蚊子！
Fucking mosquitoes!
嗨，伙计，我这里有驱蚊水要不
Hey, man. I got some spray if you want.
好啊
Yeah.
真好，谢谢
Sweet. Thanks.
你相不相信这个鬼故事啊？
Do you believe the whole ghost story about this place?
我相信那只是个传说
I believe there was a story,
但也相信有能伤人的东西
but I believe there's a ghost that can actually hurt somebody.
对，我在想
Right. Look, I've been thinking
如果鬼魂真的现身伤害我们
if a ghost takes on physical presence and manifests itself,
我们怎么阻止他？
then what's to stop it from going after somebody?
你少看点科幻频道的节目吧
Damn, man, you need to stop watching The Syfy Channel.
他要是敢出现，我就打爆他的头
If that ghost does manifest his ass, I'll shoot his head off.
来点驱虫水吗？
Hey, man, you want some bug spray?
他不怎么爱讲话是吧？
Man, he don't talk a lot, huh?
谁啊，约翰？才不是，他很搞笑的
What, who, John? No, man he's a riot.
他曾经把假发反着戴，搞笑极了
He used to do stand-up down at Fancy Wigs, man. Real hilarious.
- 真的？ - 不
- Seriously?  - No.
嘿，伙计，少抽点
Hey, man, careful with 'em cigarettes.
会让你丧命的
They'll kill you, you know.
闭嘴，查德
Shut up, Chad.
蠢货！
Dicks!
我们到底去哪儿？
Well, where the hell are we going?
我不知道，行吗
I don't know, okay.
我们走的是另一条路
We came in a different way.
你到底想让我们走多远，小丫头？
Just how much farther in you expect us to go, little girl?
我要离船近点儿
Yeah. I'd like to stay closer to the boats.
我们从那儿过来的，所以船就在正后方
Uh, we came in through there, so the boats are a straight shot back.
现在干什么呢？
So what now?
包围这一区域
Let's surround the area,
如果维克多真的存在，我们就应该在这找到他
if Victor Crowley really does exist, this is where we find him.
这算是维克多的召唤？
So is this some kind of Victor Crowley call or something?
现在呢，兵分几路？
So, what, we break up into groups?
不
No.
那不是个好主意
That's a bad idea.
不，他是对的
No, no. He's right.
那样的话我们就能走到更多地方
That way, we can cover more ground.
如果看见那怪物就开枪
All right now, if you see that monster out there, shoot.
等一下
Now, wait just a damn minute.
我可不希望一群吓坏了的人朝周围乱开枪
We don't want a bunch of spooked people walking around this swamp shooting at everything.
你说谁吓坏了？
Man, who you calling spooked?
我跟大个儿一起
I'm going with the big guy.
滚一边去
The fuck you are, boy.
别妨碍我赚钱
I'm fixin' to keep a eye on my money.
咱们快点找到那个棚子然后离开这儿
Come on, let's find that shed and get out of here.
等一下
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
有什么计划吗？
What's the plan?
计划？
The plan?
日出之后船上集合
We meet back at the boat at sun up.
找到怪物，带他的头回来…五千块
And if you do find that monster, bring back his head... 5K.
特伦特，你跟我们一其
Trent, you come with us.
你要干什么？
What do you want to do?
今晚跟这些人呆在一起
Stick with these guys tonight.
等到明天，然后出去
Wait here till tomorrow and get out of here.
好了，这个猎人是艾迪老爹
Well, all right, this hunter's Daddy Eddy.
我不想整晚跟这些傻瓜在一起
I don't want to hang out with these idiots all night.
好吧，跟我来
All right, come on.
哇，哇，嘿，兄弟，你要带着美女去沼泽？
Whoa-whoa, hey, man, what, you're going to take the pretty thing in the swamp with you?
是的，我们没事
Yeah, man. We're cool.
多谢
Thanks.
懂了
Oh, okay, I get it.
你们是一对儿对吧？
Y'all a couple or something, huh?
是我不好
My bad.
伙计，我有个想法，我们分开怎么样？
Hey man, I got an idea. Why don't we all just split up?
嗨，咱们去裸泳吧？
Hey, better yet, let'sjust go skinny dipping.
嘿，我不认识你
Hey, I don't know about you.
我要抓一条鳄鱼，在船这儿等着
I'm gonna go catch me a gator, hang out down by the boats.
我喜欢在船那儿等着
Well, I like the idea of sticking near them boats.
不过别丢下我
I don't want nobody leaving without me.
跟着我混，不吃亏
Stick with me, pal. Make it worth our while.
就剩咱们俩了
And then, it wasjust us.
害怕不？
Are you scared, man?
嘘！
Boo!
哦！
Ow.
妈的！
Damn it!
满沼泽的鳄鱼我居然打不中一条！
Swamp overflowing with gators and I can't hit one!
你得先引诱它过来
You gotta lead it more.
伙计，我知道怎么打猎
Dude, I know how to hunt.
是啊，所以才会不停的射空
Yeah. That's why you keep missing.
咱们就在这儿站一晚上吗？
So, uh, are we supposed to stand around here all night?
除非你想跟那帮混蛋呆在一起
Unless you want to go sniffing around in there with them assholes.
不
No, no.
呆在这儿倒没什么，但是五千块啊…
I'm good here but, man, 5000 bucks...
抓一个小孩子讲的故事里的人？
To hunt down a children story?
祝你好运！
Good luck!
祖比之所以悬赏那么多
And the only reason Zombie's even offering that reward,
是因为根本就不存在维克多・克劳利
because there ain't no Victor Crowley.
我们就是呆一晚上
I mean, we're gonna end up staying up all night
然后回去宣布沼泽已经清理过了
just so we can go back and declare the swamp safe and
他好能宣传旅游罢了
be able to start up his tours or some bullshit.
你怎么知道故事不是真的？
How do you know the story ain't real?
拜托
Please.
如果是真的…
If that story was real...
我是说如果我觉得故事是真的
I mean, if I even thought that story was real,
我就不会过来了
my ass wouldn't be here right now.
好吧，看见它在往右边挪了吗？
All right, see how he's moving to the right?
闭嘴
Shut up.
向右游了两英尺
Two feet to the right.
闭嘴
Shut up.
耶！哇噢！
Yeah! Whoo!
看到没？
Did you see that?
等着，闭嘴
Wait. Shut up.
你听到声音了吗？
Did you hear something?
- 我听到鳄鱼说要跟我回家  - 不是的！嘘！
- Yeah, I heard that gator decide to come home with me, that's what I heard.  - No! Shh!
听
Listen.
哦，得了
Oh, come on.
好吧，我们能够听到你弗农，真好笑
All right, we hear you Vernon. It's funny.
是弗农吗？
That was Vernon?
当然
Of course, it was.
我看到他了
I see him.
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
就在我们前面
It's out in front of us.
弗农？
Vernon?
别闹了，不然你会挨枪子儿的
Cut it out or you're gonna get hurt.
好的
Yeah.
我没跟你闹
I'm serious.
马上住口，不然我开枪了
Knock it off right now or you're gonna get shot.
我真开枪了啊
I'm serious now.
哦，靠！
Oh! Oh, fuck!
不！不！不！
No! No! No!
不！
No!
老大，等等
Hey, boss, hold on.
怎么
Come on.
我们到底干什么来了？
What are we really doing here?
穿过这里，找到船上的人
We're gonna go through there, get the people that were on that boat,
把他们带回家
and we're gonna bring them back home.
少来，我不是傻瓜
Come on. I'm not an idiot, okay.
为什么要这么多人，带这么多枪？
Why do you need all these people? Why all the guns?
好吧
All right,
听我说，贾斯汀
listen to me, Justin.
听我说
Listen to me.
如果那女孩说的是真的，维克多还在这里
If what the girl is saying is correct and Victor Crowley is still out there,
我知道怎么弄死他
I know how to get rid of him.
怎么结束诅咒
I know how to end the curse.
怎么做？
And how is that?
- 看见前面的两个人了吗？ - 是的
- You see those two right there?  - Yeah.
克劳利被杀死那天晚上他们就在那儿
They were out here the night that Crowley got murdered.
房子被点着那晚？？
Oh, the night the house got lit on fire?
是的
Yes.
他们有三个人
There were three of them.
萨姆森，那女孩儿的父亲也在其中
Samson, the girl's father, was the other one.
也就是说杀了他俩，维克多就罢手了
So that means there's only two more to go
他的仇就报了
before his revenge is satisfied
诅咒解除，沼泽就是我的
and the curse will be lifted, and the swamp is mine.
等等，这有点像谋杀
Wait. That's... that's like murder.
我伤害任何人了吗？
Am I hurting anybody?
我强迫任何人来了吗？
Did I twist anybody's arm to come out here?
他们都是自愿的
They came here on their own free will.
因为你收买了他们
Yeah, because you bribed them.
你有意见？
You got a problem with this, Justin?
对我有意见？
Do you have a problem with me?
我…
Ljust...
没意见
No.
我只想找到肖恩然后离开
Look, I just wanna find Shaun and get the hell out of here.
肖恩还好吗？
Is Shaun all right?
不知道
I don't know.
就算你知道也不会告诉我对吧？
But you wouldn't tell me the truth if you did know, would you?
看着我
Look at me.
那女孩儿也不知道肖恩的情况
The girl doesn't know what happened to Shaun either.
队伍走散了
The group got split up.
但我确定他一定在什么地方
But I'm sure he's out there somewhere.
他会没事的，相信我
He'll be fine. Trust me.
我们现在必须团结
Now we all have to stick together.
一切都会没事的
Everything is going to be fine.
他很强的
He's a tough kid.
他没那么强
He ain't that tough.
快点！
Come on.
啊！
Ah.
你一点也不想溜走？
You're not the least bit creeped out here?
你真的害怕？
You're really freaked out, huh?
是的
Well, yeah.
没必要害怕
You don't need to be scared.
而且就算真的有怪物扑过来
Besides, if a monster comes to get you,
我们有枪呢，对吧？
we've got guns, right?
我猜是的
I guess.
还记得高中时候吗
Remember... remember in high school,
我告诉你我病了所以没法考驾照
when I told you I couldn't get my driver's license because I was sick
最后没拿到驾照？
and couldn't make it to the DMV?
是的
Yeah.
我说谎了
I lied.
我考试没通过
And I failed.
教练叫我平行停车但我却撞上了别的车
Guy told me to parallel park and I totally nailed the other car.
怎么想起说这个？
Where did that come from?
我也不知道
I don't know.
只是想说而已
I guess I... I just felt like saying it.
想知道些秘密吗？
Want to know something?
什么？
What?
我知道的
I knew.
怎么知道的？
How?
记得我姑姑吗？
Remember my Aunt May?
她在汽车管理部工作，都告诉我了
She worked at the DMV. She told me the whole thing.
- 真的？ - 是的
- Really?  - Yeah.
为什么一直不跟我说？
Then why didn't you ever call me on it?
因为我当时喜欢你，不想你出丑
'Cause I had a crush on you and I felt bad, I guess.
别说了
Stop.
不
No.
你知道我仍然关心你吧？
Wait, you know I still care about you, right?
我…我…我不知道这算什么
I don't... I don't... I don't know what's going on.
管他呢
Fuck it.
这儿！在这儿
Here! It's here.
他们在这儿
They're in here.
他们本在这里的
They were here.
他们两个的尸体
Both of them, their bodies were right here.
嘘，没事的
Shh, it's okay.
嘘，嘘，嘘
Shh, shh, shh.
高兴了？
Are you happy now?
我只是来帮忙的
Hey, I'm just trying to help.
我确定他们就在这儿的
Look, I'm sure they were here,
现在却什么都没有了
but, look, there's nothing here now!
就在这儿
They were right there.
或许是另一个房子吧？
Well then, maybe... maybe it was a different shed.
- 或许你惊吓过度  - 不，我看见了
- Maybe you were just scared.  - No, I know what I saw.
我亲眼所见
I saw them with my own eyes.
或许维克多把他们带进屋里了
Crowley, maybe... maybe he took them inside the house.
玛丽贝斯！
Marybeth!
这个女孩儿吓坏了…
Hey, the girl's had quite a scare...
勇敢的姑娘
Brave little gal.
嘿，你们不能进去！
Hey, you just can't run up there!
随他们去吧
Oh, let them go.
老板，你不介意的话，我想是时候找我弟弟了
Boss, if you don't mind, I'd really like tojust find my brother
完事早点儿离开
and get the fuck out of here.
不行，大家在一起才安全
No, it's safer if we stick together.
肖恩！
Shaun!
- 肖恩！ - 孩子
- Shaun!  - Son,
我再给你最后一次警告，别喊了
I'm gonna give you about one more second to knock that shit off.
妈的
Fuck.
喜欢吗？
You like that?
是的
Yes.
Yes. Fuck.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
怀念吗？
Did you miss that?
是的，确实怀念
I did. I really did.
有多怀念？
Oh, how much? How much you missed it?
相当的
The most.
没法更怀念了
The most amount.
比冰激凌更爽吧？
You like this better than ice cream?
是的
Yep.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
- 比巧克力冰激凌也爽？ - 是的
- Better than chocolate ice cream?  - Yep.
去他妈的巧克力冰激凌
Fuck chocolate ice cream.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
爱这个胜过耶稣？
You like this better than Jesus?
这话不太合适
That'sjust... that's not appropriate.
比小耶稣呢？
Oh, you like this better than Baby Jesus?
差不多吧
Ah, about... about an equal amount.
哦耶
Oh, yeah.
爱我吗？
You love me?
什么？
What?
你爱我吗？
Do you love me?
是
Yep.
有多爱？
How much do you love me?
爱
Yep.
- 什么？我听不见  - 嗯？
- What? I can't hear you.  - Huh?
说你爱我
Tell me you love me.
我爱你
I love you.
说，说你爱我
Say it. Say you love me.
说
Say it!
- 说你爱我！ - 我爱你
- Tell me you love me!  - I love you.
我爱你，我爱你
I love you. I love you.
真的
Yeah, you do.
噢！
Oh!
就这样
Easy!
继续
C'mon!
继续啊
用力
Come on.
你不是又睡着了吧？
You didn't fall asleep on me again, did you?
上帝啊！
Oh, my God!
上帝啊！上帝啊！
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
够了！
Enough!
受够你们的神经了
Enough of this insanity. Come on.
他们在这儿
They're here.
他们一定在某什么地方
They have to be here somewhere.
我们现在就离开
Come on, we're leaving right now.
求你了，鲍勃叔叔，请相信我
Please, please, Uncle Bobby, you have to believe me.
明天白天来
Well, then, we'll come back tomorrow during the day.
让警察一起来
We'll bring the sheriff with us.
老大！
Boss!
警察不会来的…
The sheriff isn't gonna be here...
我现在就想离开！
I really wanna get out of here now!
还不可以
Not yet.
吓死我了
Please. I'm fucking scared.
那就回船上去
Then get back to the boat.
我可以拿着钥匙回去吗？
Can I get the keys back?
把我留这儿？
And leave me here?
不，我不走，我要等着
No. I won't leave. I'll wait.
你也要
The hell you will.
我会和你在一起
I'm with your boy.
我们在这儿是自找麻烦
We're looking for serious trouble being in here.
太迟了
It's too late.
关上门！
Shut the door!
Shut the fucking door!
帮我一把
Come on, give me a hand.
来啊，来啊，来啊，来啊！
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
来啊，来啊
Come on, come on.
加油
Come on, man.
推，快推
Come on push, push fast.
你们到底做了什么？
What the hell have you done?
离我远点，老头
Back off of me, old man.
你要让我们所有人都被杀死吗？
You're gonna get us all killed?
你？
You?
你在指责我？
You're blaming me?
什么？
What?
你做说什么？
What are you talking about?
你最好闭嘴！
Y'all better shot the fuck up!
嘿，你们听到了吗？
Hey, man, you hear that?
嘿，别开这种玩笑
Hey, if somebody's joking around out there, this shit ain't funny.
我们会朝你开枪的
We will shoot you.
出来，不然我们会把你的头打下来
Show yourself or we will shoot your head off.
最后一次警告！
Last warning, asshole!
开枪
Shots fired.
或许他们打到他了
Maybe they got him.
别去，呆在我这儿
No, no. Stay with me.
不
No.
我不能，我不能呆在这儿
Look, I can't. Look, I can't. I can't be in here.
或者我回船上去
Or I need to get back to the boat.
我只是想找到肖恩回家
I just wanna find Shaun and go home.
肖恩…他死了没？
Shaun... is he, is he dead?
他们都死了
They are all dead.
你骗了我们？
And you lied?
我早告诉他了
I told him the truth.
你知道我弟弟死了！
You knew my brother was dead!
安静
Quiet, kid!
这个疯婆子也就告诉我这么多
All right, all I know is what that crazy gal said.
你弟弟一定在什么地方
For all I know he could still be out there somewhere.
他没有
He's not.
要是他们误伤了然怎么办？
Well, what if you shot one of the other guys, man?
有人吗？
Hello?
怎么了？！
What the fuck?!
妈的！
Oh, shit!
真他妈倒霉！
We're fucked in here!
他妈的倒霉！
We're fucked. We're so fucked!
听我说你这个胆小鬼
Listen to me you little piece of shit.
现在好好跟着我，别做傻事
Now you stay with me and you don't do anything stupid.
如果我猜的没错
Now if I'm right
克劳利杀了他俩报了仇
and Crowley gets his revenge on those two people that killed him.
他就不会再杀人了
He's gonna have his peace.
一切就结束了我们就富有了
This will all be over and we'll be rich.
- 万一…  - 别傻了
- What if...  - Don't be a fool.
和我呆在一起
Stay with me. Stay with me.
把枪给我
Give me your gun.
不！
No!
看到什么东西了吗？
Do you see anything out there?
没有
No.
但是恐怕这不是屋子的唯一入口
But I find it hard to believe that this door is the only way in.
我去看看
I'll scope it out.
听我说，你藏起来
Now, you listen to me. I want you to hide.
不要
I'm not hiding.
够了
That's enough.
马上藏起来！
Now you hide!
快
Come on.
Come on!
我这辈子没这么害怕过
I've never been so fucking scared in my life.
你哥哥的事深表遗憾
I'm sorry about your brother.
你本可以早告诉我
You could have told me earlier.
我以为祖比会告诉你
I thought Zombie would have told you.
你确定？
Are you positive?
确定他死了？
But are you sure he's dead?
你怎么回来的？
Why the hell would you come back here?
我不明白
I don't understand.
我家人死了
My family is gone.
一无所有了
I have nothing.
我要维克多死
I wanna see Crowley die.
- 但如果他是鬼…  - 我昨晚打伤他了
- But if he's a ghost...  - I hurt him last night.
如果他能感受到痛，就能打死
If he can feel pain, then he can die.
他和你说什么？
What did he say to you?
我听见他说“他们两个”？
I heard him say something about "those two"?
好像是特伦特和你叔叔…
He seems to think that Trent and that guy with you, your uncle...
鲍勃？
Bob?
他说他们是多年以前杀死维克多的人
He says that they're with your father when they killed Victor Crowley years ago.
什么？
What?
他说如果维克多杀了他们俩
He thinks that if Victor Crowley has his revenge on them that
诅咒就解除了，一切都安全了
the curse will be lifted and he'll just go away, and they will be safe.
所以把他们带了进来？
That's why he brought us here?
我什么都不知道
I don't know shit.
- 我只知道…  - 鲍勃叔叔！
- All I know is...  - Uncle Bob!
嘿，不要！嘿！
Hey, no! Hey!
蜘蛛
Spiders.
妈的
Oh, shit.
蜘蛛
Oh, please, spiders.
妈的
Please.
妈的！
Oh, fuck!
鲍勃叔叔！鲍勃叔叔！
Uncle Bob! Uncle Bob!
这是个圈套！
It's a trap!
什么？
What?
祖比牧师，他要…
Reverend Zombie, he's trying to get...
他在屋子里！
He's in the house!
等下！不要！不不，等等！
Wait, no! No, no, wait! Wait!
杀了我吧！
Just kill me!
哦…哦，上帝啊！
Oh... Oh, God!
鲍勃叔叔，求你了！别去！
Uncle Bob, please! Don't go!
他就是想让你去呢
This is what he wants.
请听我说
Please listen to me.
帮帮我！请帮帮我！
Help! Please help me!
帮帮我！
Help me!
等等
Wait.
快，起来
Come on, get up. Come on.
鲍勃叔叔，起来
Uncle Bob, get up.
快点，我们得马上离开
Hurry! We have to get out of here.
起来，跑！
Get up. Run!
噢，不！噢，不！
Oh, no! Oh, no!
你干什么？
What are you doing?
我在救你
I'm trying to save you.
滚开
Yeah, you fuck!
不要！
No, please!
鲍勃叔叔！
Uncle Bob!
叔叔！
把她放下！
Put her down!
你要干什么！
What are you doing? Please!
哦，上帝啊！停下！
Oh, God! Please stop!
我在救你
I'm trying to save you.
- 我知道你想他死  - 不
- I know you were gonna kill him.  - No.
听我说！
Listen to me!
他会杀了你
Listen to me. He's going to kill you.
你会害死他！
You, you're gonna kill him!
不，你会害死他
No, you're gonna kill him.
- 不！ - 别把我锁在这儿！
- No!  - Don't lock me in here!
鲍勃叔叔！
Uncle Bob!
不，求你了！别丢下我
No, please! Don't leave me.
- 等等！ - 你想让他也弄死你吗？
- Wait!  - You want him to get you too?
- 好吧  - 你想活，不是吗？
- All right.  - You wanna be safe, don't you?
不要
Come on, come on.
鲍勃叔叔！
Uncle Bob!
祖比！
Zombie!
你不能把我和这东西留在一起
Zombie, you can't leave me with this thing!
- 鲍勃叔叔  - 你得帮我
- Uncle Bob!  - You gotta help me!
回来！
Come back!
祖比！
Zombie!
来吧，你这刀疤脸！
Come on you hatchet-faced fuck!
上帝啊！
Oh, God!
鲍勃叔叔！
Uncle Bob!
就快结束了，小姑娘
Now, now, little girl. It's almost over.
就结束了
It's almost all over.
不
No!
都结束了小姑娘
Now, it's all over, little girl.
都结束了
It's all over.
几十年前放火的三个孩子
Three children set that house on fire decades ago,
三个害死了维克多・克劳利的孩子
three children murdered Victor Crowley,
特伦特，你父亲，你父亲的兄弟，鲍勃叔叔
Trent, yourfather, and your father's brother, your uncle.
唯一清理沼泽和永久破除诅咒的方法
The only way to rid this swamp of that ghost's curse forever
就是让他们偿命
is to let him have revenged on the men that killed him.
看到了吗？
You see?
看到了吗！
You see!
结束了！
It's over!
维克多走了
Victor Crowley is gone.
走了！
Gone!
沼泽是我的了！
The swamp is mine.
你是个杀人犯
You're a murderer.
你就没想过要帮我
You never wanted to help me.
你害死了所有那些无辜的人
You killed all those innocent people.
不，不，不
No, no, no.
维克多杀了他们
Victor Crowley murdered those people.
我只是碰巧活了下来
I just happened to survive.
我会向警察告发你
I'm gonna tell the police what you did.
我会告诉所有人
I'm gonna tell everybody.
那你就错了，玛丽贝斯・丹斯顿
That's where you're wrong, Marybeth Dunston.
你错了
Well, there's something that you got wrong.
什么？
What?
那不是我的亲叔叔
That wasn't my real uncle.
他是我父亲的好朋友而已
Bob was my daddy's best friend.
我的亲叔叔在我十二岁那年就得白血病死了
My daddy's brother died from leukemia when I was 12.
你他妈骗我呢吧
You gotta be fuckin' kiddin' me.
死吧，给我去死吧！
Die, you motherfucker!
下地狱吧！
Go to hell!
去死吧！
Fuck you!
-= THE LAST FANTASY =-
TLF字幕组欢迎你，诚邀有志之士
tlfsubs.eastgame.org
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者